<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Choose Your Own Adventure</string>
    <string name="story1">The Wizard\'s Journey</string>
    <string name="switchString">Path choice undoable</string>

    <!--    <string name="nodeValue"></string>-->
    <!--    <string name="nodeQuestion"></string>-->
    <!--    <string name="nodeDecision1"></string>-->
    <!--    <string name="nodeDecision2"></string>-->

    <string name="returnButton">Return to start</string>
    <string name="menuButton">Return to menu</string>
    <string name="undoButton">Undo</string>

    <string name="node1Value">You\'re a wizard  on your way to get a magical flower for your potions. The flower only blooms on a blue moon, three days from now. You set out from your hovel and head onto the winding path.</string>
    <string name="node1Question">The forrest path forks, the left path twists, heading up a mountain path, the right side leading by a river. Which do you choose?</string>
    <string name="node1Decision1">Mountain path</string>
    <string name="node1Decision2">River path</string>

    <string name="node2Value">You take the mountain path, it leads past a the entrance to what looks like a cave. You think you see something gliter from the dark within. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="node2Question">Investigate the cave entrance or continue on your long way around the mountain?</string>
    <string name="node2Decision1">Investigate</string>
    <string name="node2Decision2">Continue</string>

    <string name="node3Value">You enter the cave. The glimmer seems to have been from trails of gold piled up ahead, how do you want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="node3Question">Use some magic concealment or grab the gold and leg it?</string>
    <string name="node3Decision1">Grab the gold</string>
    <string name="node3Decision2">Use magic</string>

    <string name="node4Value">Thinking of all the wide sleeve robes you could buy, you approach the pile of gold. As you make it within a few feet of the gold, the mound growing as more of the cave becomes visible, it stirs suddenly. The gigantic head of a dragon protrudes from the mound of gold, you try to turn back but too late! The dragon having spotted you, raises its head and decimates you with it\'s fiery breath. Your body falls to ash, a fitting death for a greedy thief.</string>

    <string name="node5Value">You cast a spell of concealment on yourself and cautiosuly make your way to the pile of gold, more appearing as you see the size of the cave ahead. while observing the mound you realise it\'s moving steadily up and down, a dragon lurks within, waiting to prey on the greedy. You spot light from a tunnel on the other side of the gold.</string>
    <string name="node5Question">Turn back and continue up the mountain or see where the tunnel leads?</string>
    <string name="node5Decision1">(unfinished)</string>
    <string name="node5Decision2">Turn back</string>

    <string name="node6Value">You make your way further up the mountain...</string>
    <string name="node6Question"></string>
    <string name="node6Decision1"></string>
    <string name="node6Decision2"></string>

</resources>
